(Sheldon:)Very well.
So where
should we do it?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'll just Google
"hot, dark and moist,"
(Sheldon:)see what comes up.
(Raj:)Uh, Sheldon...
(Sheldon:)Oh, there, well, look,
there's all kinds of videos.
(knocking)
(Leonard:)Hey, you got a sec?
(Penny:)Hi. Sure.
(Leonard:)I was hoping we could talk
about the money again.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie,
just forget about it.
No, no, no, no,
(Leonard:)hear me out. I know things
got a little weird last night.
(Penny:)Well, leaving an envelope full
of cash on my dresser after sex
(Penny:)would count as weird.
(Leonard:)Well, I think I came up
with a pretty good solution.
(Leonard:)Mm.
Why don't we just put the money
in a joint account?
(Leonard:)It'll be our first
money together.
(Leonard:)We can use it for the wedding,
the honeymoon, whatever.
(Penny:)You know what, that's great.
I love that!
(Leonard:)Yeah, of course you do--
I'm not just a genius in bed.
(feminine voice):
You sure are, baby.